All dressed up and everywhere to go.
Romance in Style is a tv movie, comedy, romance
film directed by Michael Robison.
Ella's unique designs inspire publishing mogul Derek to
include plussized fashion in his magazine.
It's not long before Derek realizes that Ella's
influence reaches far beyond the catwalk.
Ella, played by Jaicy Elliot.
Derek, played by Benjamin Hollingsworth.
Katie, played by Connie Manfredi.
Liza, played by Jorja Cadence.
Oscar, played by Daylin Willis.
Claudia, played by Laura Soltis.
Persuasion is a 2022 American historical romance  film based
on Jane Austen's 1817 novel of the same name.
It was directed by Carrie Cracknell from a screenplay
by Ron Bass and Alice Victoria Winslow.
The film stars Dakota Johnson, Cosmo Jarvis, Nikki
Amuka-Bird, Mia McKenna-Bruce, Richard E.
Grant, and Henry Golding.
Persuasion was released to theaters in the United States on July 8, 2022, a
week before its streaming release on July 15, 2022, by Netflix.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.